(Sheldon:)Hardly.
(Sheldon:)Consider this unlikely
but very plausible scenario.
(Sheldon:)A young woman alone
in the big city.
(Sheldon:)Her ridiculous dream
(Sheldon:)of becoming an actress
lies shattered about her.
(Penny:)Hey, wait a minute.
(Howard:)Well, hang on. Let's
see where he's going.
(Sheldon:)Then it hits her.
(Sheldon:)How is she going to survive?
(Sheldon:)I mean, she has no prospects,
no marketable skills.
(Sheldon:)And then one day,
(Sheldon:)she meets a group of geniuses
(Sheldon:)and their friend Howard.
(Howard:)Hey, I...
(Howard:)Hang on.
Let's see where he's going.
(Sheldon:)She befriends them,
and then lies in wait
(Sheldon:)until they reveal
a marketable idea,
(Sheldon:)which she steals
and sells to the highest bidder.
- That is ridiculous.
- Oh, is it?
(Sheldon:)Let's see you come up
with an explanation
(Sheldon:)as to why this woman hangs out
with us all the time.
(Penny:)Oh, great. You know what?
(Penny:)I've already mooched
dinner off you guys.
(Penny:)I don't need to listen to this.
(Howard:)There's your answer--
free food.